Guide to the David Price Papers, 1960-2006 and undated RL.01048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Additions to the collection, 15 boxes
  - Accession (2016-0138), 1995-1998 and undated
    - Newt Gingrich ethics case, 1997 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Visits, 1996 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Funerals, 1995-1998 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Phone records, 1995-1996 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - MLK Speech, 1998 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Bill Sax: Minority Business Consulting Program, Fuqua, 1996 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Jewish National Fund, 1997 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Form letters to constituents, 1990s (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - House oversight, 1996-1997 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - American Folklife Center in the Library of Congress, 1997 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 2)
    - Daily schedules, Congress, 1991-1993, 1997 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 3)
    - "Case work", 1996 (Box Acc. 16/138: Box 3)